{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Everything in React is a __________",
            "answers": [
                "Module",
                "Component",
                "Hooks",
                "Template"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
            "answers": [
                "Original DOM",
                "Virtual DOM",
                "Both A & B",
                "None Of The Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following acts as the input of a class-based component?",
            "answers": [
                "Class",
                "Factory",
                "Render",
                "Props"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What is ReactJs?",
            "answers": [
                "Server side framework ",
                "A Library for building interaction interfaces ",
                "Client Side Framework ",
                "None of the Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "React is ............ Javascript library ",
            "answers": [
                "Module based",
                "Component based",
                "System based",
                "All are correct"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A valid react component can return ...... number of elements. ",
            "answers": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "None of the Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following API is a MUST for every ReactJS component? ",
            "answers": [
                "getInitialState",
                "render",
                "renderComponent",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the default port for webpack dev server? ",
            "answers": [
                "3000",
                "8080",
                "3306",
                "8809"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "React Js is developed by ",
            "answers": [
                "Google",
                "Microsoft",
                "Facebook",
                "None of the Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is a correct definition of state in react? ",
            "answers": [
                "A persistent storage ",
                "An internal data store (object) of component",
                "Both",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        }
    ]
}